it's today
I didn't sleep at all that night bro
can you believe i had 1 nightmare
I dreamed of an empty chair bro
after that event that gave 6 people
I got it on my head you know
I spent the whole dawn reviewing everything
thinking
it always seems like something is missing,
right?
and then there's that anxiety if everything will work out
if the hostel has good internet
I'm just spending dawn writing
filling my face with
to deliver the best there to
people who see value in my work
and I really hope that 1 day people
see value in your
is on
the time of truth has come
all good bye
bye
caraca hand
I would exhale
I'm already here at the bro's studio see
it's almost starting to live
I just show you a little bit here bro
how I'm preparing
I brought the little papers in my backpack
I put here
there's guys everything there already bro
I do not understand
doing this beatbox prep
I confess that there is still a lot to go
hope now for everything work out
bring 1 quality content there
and that's it we're going to march
be interesting OR uninteresting
if you have something there that you can
add to people's lives bro
divides as
stand still
charge your price
everything is fine
it's on doidão
as well as any product or service
the most important thing is the quality of what you have
no matter what you do
like you
do is we'll march here
that the bro here so cheating and I'm just freaking out
soon start living here man
so I'll close this way
gratitude
you there who are accompanying
that was the seventy
we're together until tomorrow
it will stay time eh bro
now i have to help me here
Gustavo